Matt Sanwell

Paradise Cottage Wheal Hope Goonhavern Truro TR4 9QJ

0117 230 2546 matt@designunltd.co.uk

Tessa Gendall Gendall Design Limited

Maritime House Discovery Quay Falmouth Cornwall TR11 3XA

Dear Mrs Gendall

I wish to apply for the role of Senior Digital Web Developer, currently being advertised on linkedin.com. Please find enclosed my CV for your consideration. This role is a fantastic opportunity for me to work for large brands that are household names and I am excited at the prospect of collaborating as part of an in house team for Gendall.

As detailed in my CV I have over 18 years experience working within the web design industry; the majority being development orientated. Through experience of running my own businesses, I understand the importance of client care and fostering strong relationships built on trust. Many of my clients have been with me for over 15 years and it is my ability to work through challenges that has preserved these relationships.

In my current position I work with freelancers and have gained the skills to communicate clearly and efficiently as well as manage multiple projects at the same time. I feel that I could bring not only my creative and technical expertise to this role, but my ability to provide a bespoke and tailored approach with attention to detail for your existing and potential clients.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to the prospect of meeting with you to discuss my application further.

Yours sincerely, Matt Sanwell

MATT SANWELL

Curriculum vitae

From a background in graphic design, I moved into web development, where I have specialised in cutting edge web based applications within the MAMP environment. Having run my own companies, I am self motivated, but also work well as part of a team and I am used to juggling multiple projects and taking direction from others. I have worked on a range on regional and national brands and have retained key clients through an excellent eye for detail and the ability to deliver projects on time and on budget. I constantly strive to improve my repertoire of skills and feel that personal development is imperative in this fast moving industry.

Experience

XC Racer

www.xcracer.com

XCRacer.com allows mountain bike event organisers to run their own online booking facility, so far it has processed over £1m of entries. In addition, it has an online shop. I built this website from scratch using PHP/MySQL and it is controlled by a bespoke CMS that has different levels of administration. The front end is based on Bootstrap.

iAM Bands

www.iambands.com

I designed and built this unique website for pro UK surfer, Sam Lamiroy. Working within a tight budget, I delivered a site that utilises millions of unique reference codes, with scope for world wide growth.

iroka

www.iroka.com

iroka are one of my long term clients. Their website has a bespoke e-commerce section that uses PayPal Pro and a credit solution from Pay4Later. I have also integrated a blog and an interior design portfolio that's all controlled via an easy to use CMS.

Wed Magazine

www.wedmagazine.co.uk

I have worked with Wed since they started out and their web presence is a prominent part of their business. wedmagazine.co.uk is driven by a bespoke CMS which allows them to control their wedding directory and add editorial content. It was important that the site was ranked on the first page for many competitive search phrases on the major search engines. The site now generates a considerable amount of the company's profit.

BT World Wheelchair Rugby Challenge

www.wwrc15.com

Working with the key sponsor and the RFU to design and build a website to promote the upcoming event.

Paradise Cottage Wheal Hope Goonhavern Truro TR4 9QJ

DOB: 23/03/77

0117 230 2546 matt@designunltd.co.uk

www.designunltd.co.uk

Employment

2004 - Present

DesignUNLTD [Director]

Bespoke web development for regional and national clients

2000 - 2004

After Dark Media Ltd (Director),
Responsible for 7 employees in a
design/publishing agency

1999 - 2000 Freelance Design and Print

1997 - 1999

Ran company website and marketing

Education

PCAD, Plymouth 1995-1997 Graphic Design - HND

CRC, Cambridge 1993 -1995 General Art & Design - ND

Skills

HTML/CSS/JQUERY

PHP/MySQL/PHPMyADMIN

ADOBE CC InDesign/Photoshop/Illustrator

Interests

Surfing, Windsurfing, Mountain Biking, Snowboarding, Surf Lifesaving and Music. I am a member of the St Agnes Coast Guard Cliff Rescue Team